<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <!-- Default -->
	<string name="txt_header_default">Information</string>

    <!-- Calculator -->
    <string name="txt_calculator_header">Calculator</string>
    <string name="txt_calculator_paragraph1">A standard calculator that allows you to chain commands with the last one used.
        Can also represent the numbers in binary representation. Due to space issues, binary numbers will only use integers.
        \n\n <i>Please note that using a minus sign (-) is not the correct
        way of representing negative values in binary. It is just used here for easier usage of the calculator to quickly test out
        various calculations and see their corresponding value.</i></string>

    <!-- Character Converter -->
    <string name="txt_char_conv_header">Character Converter</string>
    <string name="txt_char_conv_paragraph1">Write any number of characters and these will be converted to their respective
        ASCII representation in decimal and hexadecimal. If a number is entered it will instead get processed to show what ASCII character that number represents.
        \n\nUsing a non numeric character the converter will process these one at a time, however in the case of integers 
        these will all be processed as a unit in order to be able to represent the full ASCII range.\n\n
        I.e. Entering e38yu will be split into e, 68, y, u and show the ASCII value of e, y and u while the 68 will show the value of the
        character that it represents, in this case \'D\'.</string>

    <!-- Note Pad -->
    <string name="txt_note_pad_header">Note Pad</string>
    <string name="txt_note_pad_paragraph1">A standard note pad that saves individual notes on the phone. Will save upon pressing back but
        only if something was changed in the note.\n\nTo delete a note do a long press on the note you wish to delete.</string>

    <!-- Decider -->
    <string name="txt_decider_header">Decider</string>
    <string name="txt_decider_paragraph1">The tool for those with decision agony. Will tell you whether to do or don\'t (Please don\'t base 
        serious decisions on this). Will also save how many times <i>Yes</i> and <i>No</i> have been randomly chosen, for posterity. \n\nThe other half of the activity 
        gives a random number from an interval passed in by you. This can be thought of as an n-sided dice.</string>

    <!-- Scrum Poker -->
    <string name="txt_scrum_poker_header">Scrum Poker</string>
    <string name="txt_scrum_poker_paragraph1">A list of all the cards in standard scrum poker. Simply press the card you want to focus. 
        Press the focused card or the back button to minimise it.</string>

</resources>